quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "Name an additional desirable security property?",
        "correct_answer": "Authenticity",
        "options": ["Authenticity", "Reliability", "Security clearance", "Connectivity"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the 'I' stand for in the CIA model for cybersecurity?",
        "correct_answer": "Integrity",
        "options": ["Integrity", "Information", "Intelligence", "IP"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the subnet mask for the following network 192.168.0.1/25?",
        "correct_answer": "255.255.255.128",
        "options": ["255.255.255.128", "255.255.255.192", "255.255.255.0", "255.255.0.224"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is an attack vector?",
        "correct_answer": "Malware",
        "options": ["A weak password", "Loss of intellectual property", "Script kiddie", "Malware"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these is a threat?",
        "correct_answer": "Script kiddie",
        "options": ["Loss of intellectual property", "Script kiddie", "A weak password", "Malware"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does DAC stand for?",
        "correct_answer": "Discretionary access control",
        "options": ["Direct access control", "Discretionary access control", "Discretion access control", "Designed access control"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default TTL for Microsoft Windows 7 Professional?",
        "correct_answer": "128",
        "options": ["32", "128", "254", "64"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What does CVE stand for?",
        "correct_answer": "Common vulnerability exposure",
        "options": ["Common vulnerability element", "Computer vulnerability element", "Common vulnerability exposure", "Computer vulnerability exposure"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Identify the lower Layer 4 layers of the OSI model in the correct order.",
        "correct_answer": "Physical, Datalink, Network, and Transport",
        "options": [
            "Physical, Datalink, Transport, and Network",
            "Datalink, Physical, Network, and Transport",
            "Physical, Datalink, Network, and Transport",
            "Physical, Transport, Datalink, and Network"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which DNS zone contains a read/writeable copy of the DNS zone database?",
        "correct_answer": "Primary",
        "options": ["Master", "Stub Zone", "Secondary", "Primary"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which statement describes a recursive query?",
        "correct_answer": "The client makes a request of the local DNS server. The DNS server performs the remaining queries.",
        "options": [
            "The client making the DNS request queries DNS servers in turn until the IP address is found",
            "No such query in DNS",
            "The client makes a request of the local DNS server. The DNS server performs the remaining queries.",
            "The server making the DNS request queries DNS servers in turn until the IP address is found."
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following DIG commands would perform a reverse DNS lookup?",
        "correct_answer": "dig -x 100.90.80.70 +short",
        "options": ["dig -e 100.90.80.70 +short", "dig -IP 100.90.80.70 +short", "dig -x 100.90.80.70 +short", "dig -r 100.90.80.70 +short"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a defense against ARP attacks?",
        "correct_answer": "Static entries",
        "options": ["Firewall", "Static entries", "Access control lists", "Anti-malware software"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What layer of the OSI model are Media Access Control (MAC) addresses encapsulated?",
        "correct_answer": "Layer 3",
        "options": ["Layer 1", "Layer 2", "Layer 3", "Layer 4"]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bits in a MAC address?",
        "correct_answer": "48",
        "options": ["40", "32", "48", "16"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Metrics such as the attack vector, complexity, exploit maturity, and how much user interaction is required are all found in what scoring system?",
        "correct_answer": "CVSS",
        "options": ["CVE", "CVSS", "CAN", "NVD"]
    },
    {
        "question": "According to the operating protection ring model, what ring contains user programs and applications?",
        "correct_answer": "Ring 3",
        "options": ["Ring 3", "Ring 1", "Ring 2", "Ring 0"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Files, databases, computers, programs, processes, devices, and media are all examples of what?",
        "correct_answer": "Objects",
        "options": ["Subjects", "Objects", "File stores", "Users"]
    },
    {
        "question": "In the OSI model, when a packet changes from a datastream to a segment or a datagram, which layer has it traversed?",
        "correct_answer": "Transport layer",
        "options": ["Transport layer", "Application layer", "Data link layer", "Physical layer"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the primary advantage of decentralised access control?",
        "correct_answer": "It provides control of access to people closer to the resources",
        "options": ["It provides better redundancy", "It provides control of access to people closer to the resources", "It is less expensive", "It provides more granular control of access"]
    }
]
